camstudio.org 2019-07-04

# CamStudio - Our Privacy Policy

Camstudio.org is committed to protecting the privacy of our online visitors. We collect information from online visitors who ask to be on our newsletter mailing list and/or receive periodic email announcements. Anyone who wishes can choose to be removed from our mailing list at any time. 

In addition, should we at some point offer a paid subscription or support contract, online visitors who wish to purchase either through our Web site will have to provide their name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number and expiration date. All credit card transactions will occur over a secure connection. 

All online visitor data collected by Camstudio.org is protected against unauthorized access. We will not sell, trade, or give your personal information to other companies or organizations.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, Camstudio.org makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons

Camstudio.org's blog and forum **does** use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads when you visit our website. They may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

You may opt out of the use of the Google's and DoubleClick's DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy page at: 

Camstudio.org has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. Camstudio.org's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

We may use [third-party advertising companies](https://d7r1ox5aceffx.cloudfront.net/pp.html) to serve ads when you visit our website.

## **Children’s Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. Camstudio.org encourages parents to go online with their kids. Here are a few tips to help make a child's online experience safer:

Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc. 

Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate. 

Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child's information is treated. 

Check out the this article for more tips on protecting children's privacy online.:

<https://www.comparitech.com/blog/vpn-privacy/protecting-childrens-privacy/>

## Contacting Us.

We can be reached by contacting: **privacy @ camstudio . org (remove spaces)**

Click Here To Return To The Previous Page
